Yes, hello everyone!
This is Saya Kanagawa of Nogizaka46!
This time, I'd like to introduce the Kanagawa family.
Or rather, yourself.
Or rather, my relationship with my family.
I'd like to show you all.
We get along really well.
I hope you enjoy it!
Ouch!
That's great!
Thank you so much for your time.
That's what I'm talking about.
The day's
Work's over.
My mom came to pick me up.
Ta-da!
He's so cute!
Oh, he's so cute.
Wait, I'll tell you later.
I'll tell you later.
Let's go for a ride.
It's not cute.
You're not cute.
Put me down.
I can't see anything.
Nice hair.
Wait, you're right.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Oh, my God, they're here.
Yay!
So cute!
I've always wanted to look good with you, Miri-tan.
The camera's not so bad!
I'm going home.
What's wrong?
I'm tired.
Tired, tired, tired
Right now, right now.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
The youngest one loves
Grandma's
Don't wake up.
Ta-da!
It's everyone's favorite.
All right.
Heart tipple.
Garlic proof.
That's cute.
No, it's not.
Yay.
It stinks.
Cute.
It's so stinky, but it's full of it.
It's okay.
What happened to the garlic water?
It stinks and it's garlic... a lot.
But...
It stinks.
It kind of smells like...
Smells like saury.
Sunny tomorrow
Rain.
Really?
You're not so lucky. We're not so lucky.
Don't put us together.
Mom, we're in this together.
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
We're home!
Don't get upset.
Wait, I'm not having a heart attack.
I'm going to see Grandma.
Mamy?
I'll take care of you.
I'm back.
I'm back, Mami.
I'm not going home again.
That's right, I'm back from work.
You're home already?
It's fun.
Fun?
I'm home, Mami.
Thank you.
All right.
Here you go.
Rittan, come here.
Ouch.
You're so cute.
It's Rittan.
So cute!
First appearance, Mr. Patin.
What?
It's on YouTube.
Isn't it nice, Partan?
I'm Pathan.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
And I'm clean.
I'm peeled.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Go see what your mother's making.
What's in it?
This is...
Canana and berries.
Did you put the milk in with the gioghurt?
Did you put the milk in?
I put milk.
Honey.
I'm going to make acai.
Oh, look, I bought this in Singapore.
It's so cute!
Only my mom could fit in it.
When I come home in the morning, she rushes me to eat!
Don't say it, don't say it, don't say it!
Oh, my gosh! The acai is coming along.
It's not acai.
It's acai for acai's sake.
The best mama's acai I've ever had.
It's acai. It's acai.
I'll eat blueberries.
I'll eat a lot of blueberries.
Hey, hey!
It's done!
Acai balls are ready!
Ta-da!
Bittan doesn't like fruit.
Only fruit!
I love fruit!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Acai balls are so good right now!
It's so good!
Pow!
Thirty minutes, baby!
Five more minutes.
There it is. - All right.
Every time I do this, it never happens.
That was delicious! Thank you!
What, are you coming over soon?
Mommy!
You worked so hard last night to get me to bed.
Yes, good morning.
Good morning.
When? Already.
Already gone.
It's a little long, isn't it?
Just a little bit. A little bit longer.
Just a little bit longer.
Wake up.
June?
Yeah, June.
I'm not gonna say anything about recording.
Basically, I don't say little things.
Okay, so...
Welcome to the morning.
Today
With Matan
With Ma-tsan
With Ma'tan
Once
Scone shop
Tea shop
I went to a cafe
Often with my mom
I go with my mom and my mom.
Can I pick you up at the best scone shop?
But they were really good. Their scones.
You even made your own from there.
I'm in trouble.
I bought some jam in Singapore...
Ko-chan's jam...
Ko-chan's jam... and I'd eat it in the morning.
I don't know what it was, but she said it was a waste.
He said it was a waste and wouldn't eat it.
That's okay.
But I did eat some of it.
You ate some?
With what?
Soy flour.
Oh, wow.
What a waste, lady.
Awww.
Makeup and stuff.
Awww...
You know... powder.
Use it already.
And then harden it a little more.
Like, I'm still using this stuff.
Put some of this ragged stuff on a tissue.
Crush them and put the powder on them.
You're a waste of a mother, really.
I said I'd buy it for you, but I don't want it.
There's still some left.
There's no more left.
It's time to buy some more, errand boy.
When you've used it all up, every last bit.
Fun, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy
Delicious, delicious, delicious
Delicious!
When this hourglass falls
I'll push this one
Oh, it fell.
They're all down.
Do you need lift support?
No.
Straight on.
He's trying to look cool.
I'm trying to be cool. I'm trying to be cool.
I'll open the curtains.
Tastes good.
Delicious!
These are our favorite scones!
There are so many of them!
It's quite a lot.
Enough for the whole family!
This is omelette cheesecake!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
May I?
It's delicious.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum. Yum.
Okay, one more time.
Next time I see you at ProWalk, I'll try the popsicles at Gala!
Mr. 유ihara,
includes
me
this juice the day I see you eat fast!
I have something to drink every day.
Hmm? Black stroke?
This goes with the potato chips.
Hey, music.
Music.
We've arrived at your restaurant.
There are a lot of people in the clock tower.
Can we stop with the people?
It's a popular spot.
There aren't many atrosiers.
We don't go there very often. It's more for tourists.
You can go inside, right?
Yes.
Do you know why the traffic lights in Hokkaido stand still?
Because of the snow.
Ta-da!
Sudden change.
What was that?
Aren't you going to continue?
I didn't get that answer.
Soft Katsugen.
This is very popular in Hokkaido.
When I get back.
I'll buy it if it's a small size.
It's so rare. But it's there.
Actually, it's a very large size.
It's very big, 500 yen.
This one is 300 yen.
I buy it alone at the supermarket.
Oh, I heard they used to sell them.
Oh, they sold these.
I sold it!
Oh my God!
Do you want some Gelotto?
Where?
Is this it? Here?
But there's also this awesome ice cream house.
You wanna go to the ice cream house?
But we're at the exit. What do we do now?
What do we do? - Mm-hm.
There's so many different kinds.
Really?
I've always wanted to go.
I hope it snows soon.
When does it start snowing?
Not yet? Doesn't it feel good?
I haven't seen any snow bugs yet.
It's a little late for that, isn't it?
Hey, look, look, look.
Look, look, look, there's a sea of clouds.
Where is it?
It's a sea of clouds.
Sea of clouds here, gentlemen.
Ta-da!
See that? This white stuff.
Wow, that's great. That's great.
Here, here.
It's pretty much a sea of clouds right now.
Wow, a sea of clouds right there.
It's releasing when it sees the sea.
Wow, sea of clouds.
That's amazing.
I don't see it very often.
I wonder what's going on there.
Oh, my God.
Maui Hill.
It's like a loud voice.
We've arrived at Maui Hill!
Ta-da!
Do you always buy melons here?
Maui
Mr. Seika!
We always buy melons for our live concerts here.
There's a pumpkin.
What's a pumpkin?
It's a pumpkin!
It's a huge pumpkin.
I was born on Halloween.
I was born on Halloween, so there's a Halloween pumpkin here.
It's like they're celebrating my birthday.
Self-conscious? What's this?
I'll take it.
Yes, it's in Tenjikan.
It's so good!
Genghis Khan is so good!
Have you ever had it?
Yeah, I have.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Is this lamb?
Yeah, it's good.
Yum.
Mmm.
It's kind of thicker than normal, isn't it?
You guys make a bad couple.
I ordered the Delatto. Who am I?
Marron.
And you?
Cream cheese glue berry.
I had it, Delatto.
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Delicious.
So much marron...
The marron is so delicious. I recommend it.
Good night.
My sister came home.
What did she say?
She said I look great.
Everyone loved it.
She was well-received.
It was well-received.
Dad,
Papa,
Papa
This is delicious.
It's the last one.
Bon appétit.
It's better when it's warm.
It's delicious.
Jyan (rock-paper-scissors)
Whole
Cheese so bibimbap is out!
It's my favorite dish.
I'll let my mom mix it up.
It's my favorite. I'll let my mom mix it.
Really?
It looks like this.
Thank you for dinner.
Now I'd like to play some mah-jongg.
Great. Absolutely.
Do you have any snacks for Mom?
Anything?
Sweets.
I can't get anything.
And...
There he is.
What?
Shuai.
He's in.
Fierce.
Meh.
atra
Meh
TOMORROW
Osemereishon
rock, paper, scissors!
Happy Birthday
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you!
Let's go!
Move it, move it, move it.
Move, move, move.
Move, move, move
Yay!
Look at this little guy!
Rik-chan's
Rikchan's shoes.
It hurts!
I'm sorry they're yellow.
They're yellowed.
Yes, they are.
Yeah.
This is the one that's done.
Here.
That's it.
Your mom made that for you, didn't she?
Wow, that's great.
Ta-da!
I have walnuts in my house.
I have walnuts at home.
Let's try it like this.
Like this.
I've been told that if you do it in threes, it sounds quicker.
Yeah, that's what they said.
Wren, can you ride all of them?
No, sir.
You can't?
I'd rather ride the little one.
No, I can't.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Don't take Len's weight.
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle.
Back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
Wiggle your feet.
Ankle by ankle.
Ankle, ankle, ankle.
Ankle by ankle by ankle
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.